Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana,
was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's dark triad
also possessed powers from the devils of the underworld
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Get it on, get it on,始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on, hold on!
Yeah!
Never listen, fight for liberty
真実性、飲み込む常識を増え
逆境の先にある朝
Oh yeah!
幻想に埋もれた人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Loud up!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えてもかすぐしていく
Spin it!
Wake up! Yeah! Let's go!
Leave it myself!
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up!
想像せよ偽りのない自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up!
Hey yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey yeah!
Yeah!
The ground up!
Hey yeah!
Yeah!
The ground up!
While you were defending your own headquarters, the Golden Dawn's base was attacked as well.
They were almost wiped out.
I can't tell you how relieved I am to see you all survived.
That's because Asta and Yami were around.
So how bad is it?
He should pull through, fortunately.
But I'm not sure what we can do for his right arm.
There's no telling what'll come of it.
Excuse me, but would you mind taking a look at Ghosh too, please?
Was he injured as well?
The wound's all healed. I feel fine now.
You should still let him make sure, though. Just in case.
What do you mean?
Ghosh was hit with an enormous sword that went right through him, sir.
I used his spell to heal him as fast as I could, but...
I don't understand. I thought you were a transformation magic user.
Don't worry, Gray. I'll take a look.
Wait. I'm sorry. Did she say the sword went all the way through your body?
Yeah.
This goes beyond healing. It looks as though the tissue's been completely rebuilt.
Perhaps at the core of your magic, it's something much more than transformation.
Then what kind of magic is it?
I wish I could be of more help, but I honestly have no idea.
I believe this is something that Gray needs to figure out for herself.
Yes, sir.
I'd like Asta to stay here for a while so that I can monitor him.
The rest of you can return to the Black Bull's hideout.
The squad captains are holding an emergency meeting tomorrow morning.
The best thing you can do is get some rest, so you can be ready for whatever comes next.
The best thing you can do is get some rest.
I can't move my body.
Are you going somewhere?
Who is that? Is he using magic to hold me still?
You should go back inside now.
They took the captain. I have to save him.
That won't work.
You'd be walking into a fight against not only the devil-possessed man who defeated you before,
but two others who are equally powerful.
Believe me, you don't stand a chance.
Shh.
On top of that, your own devil's forsaken you, and you aren't sure what'll happen to your right arm.
How does he know that?
Challenging them in your condition isn't brave.
In fact, it's foolish and reckless.
I don't care. I still have to go.
How could I just sit around here and do nothing when he's in trouble?
When he needs my help!
He might as well leave that boorish brute to die.
Whoever you are, shut your mouth.
Because you don't know the first thing about Captain Yami.
Oh, I know him quite well.
He's a violent and vicious man.
Not to mention he's irresponsible and brash.
To tell the truth, he's worthless.
I'm gonna need backup over here.
Master?
You don't know him. You've got no idea.
Captain Yami risked his life to protect us.
And yet he still lost the battle, which proves him to be a fool.
Destroyer!
Let me go!
Shirk!
If you can't even hold your own against me, there's no possibility of you saving the Captain.
That's right.
Because you're weak.
This is all my fault.
I'm not strong enough.
But you do seem like a good person.
Which is why I like you.
No need to worry.
Yami's still alive.
Wake.
Who are you?
Tell the truth.
I'm Vice Captain Noct of the Black Bulls.
A pleasure.
I can teach you how to use your devil power.
If you would like to learn, that is.
Did he just say he's the Vice Captain of the Black Bulls?
What'd I miss, Noct?
And who's this puny guy you're talking to?
That key?
A devil?
I hate to tell you this, Gimodelo, but you're a whole lot punier than he is.
Don't even start!
You're only saying that because I'm not in my true form!
You're talking like best buddies.
You're possessed by a devil, too?
Precisely.
This little imp right here is Gimodelo.
It's our crest, so it is true.
Are you really our Vice Captain?
Yes.
Although Yami basically decided that himself.
Don't make me leave!
This whole thing is so crazy.
It's no surprise you don't know about me.
After all, I've only been to the hideout once.
And why is that?
It's because I despise Yami.
I hate to admit it, but stubborn people like him tend to be very resilient.
He's still got some time left to live.
But...
How do you know that for sure?
Well, I've been undercover in the Spade Kingdom for a long time now.
I don't know much about you.
And I'm not even sure if I can trust you.
But...
You're the only person who might know how to get Captain Yami back.
So please help me.
Teach me everything you can about my devil power.
Good.
I'm glad to see you're straightforward.
I quite like that trait in a person.
Um, thank you.
But as of right now, I can't say that I'm sensing even a smidgen of talent within you.
Huh?
Wow, tell me how you really feel.
I'm sure it'll work out if you learn to use your powers.
Yeah?
Great, let's do it.
Oh no, you need to get some rest first.
Huh?
There's somewhere I'd like to go with you tomorrow, so take it easy tonight.
You expect me to be able to sleep right now?
Just do it.
I hate selfish people.
Excellent.
It seems you're all here.
Now then, let's begin the emergency captain's meeting.
This concludes the report from the Black Bulls who witnessed the attack.
The Tree of Kleefoth.
It's supposed to connect this world to the Underworld.
And to create it, they need the magic types that William and Yami possess.
I see.
I still can't believe they kidnapped them.
I can.
Those two allowed themselves to be caught off guard.
And they dare to call themselves Magic Knight Squad Captains?
Of just a couple of lousy men.
Oh no!
My sweet Yami's been abducted!
Is he alright?
I hope they haven't heard him!
I haven't had a chance to confess my love to him yet!
We did everything that we could.
And it still wasn't enough.
The enemy wasn't even fighting us seriously.
Yeah, that's a real likely story, kid.
Sounds to me like you might have chickened out on the guy!
Turns out the Golden Dawn's got a sniveling coward for a vice-captain!
That's enough, Jack.
Those foul villains could be linking this world to the Underworld even as we speak.
Care?
Then it's all gonna be fire and brimstone, I guess.
We must prevent that outcome at all costs.
Sadly, we don't have much information.
Great!
So we're all gonna sit around and talk about it.
Genius plan you've got there.
Forget it.
This stupid meeting obviously isn't going anywhere.
I'm out!
Stop.
You'd better not be thinking about going to infiltrate Spade on your own.
Yeah, right!
Just to rescue that idiot?
Besides, even if I did, it's not like it would be any of your business!
You're a fool!
It is our business!
I won't allow a fellow captain to be so rash!
Because I want to go save Yami, too!
Well, it's better than just sitting here picking our noses all day!
Believe me, Jack, I want the chance to kill that monster just as badly as you do.
Everyone, settle down right now!
Yowl what?
Lord Julius?
Good to see you're all motivated at least.
Still though, I dislike those who can't maintain proper civility.
Uh, hi, captains!
I'd appreciate it if you would quiet down.
Set a better example.
Oh, stop.
Who is this intruder?
Declare yourself!
Please.
I can assure you that I have every right to be included in this meeting.
Whoa, you've got four devils?
I didn't expect that.
Devils?
So he's possessed as well.
Tell us, who are you?
This man is with the Black Bulls.
He's their vice-captain.
Wait, seriously?
He'd been operating in the Spade Kingdom as a spy.
However, I was unaware that he was possessed.
So that's the vice-captain of the Black Bulls?
I didn't realize we had sent a spy.
I suppose the vice-captain of Yami's squad could be practically anyone.
Have I seen this jerk?
Wait, I remember you?
Your magic is different now, though.
That man is no more.
Anyway, we're wasting time.
I suggest we get straight to the point.
I'd like you all to have a seat.
As you know, the Gate to the Underworld is about to be opened in the Spade Kingdom.
So, we can assume they're already making preparations for the ritual of the advent of Klyphoth.
To do so, they'll undoubtedly offer Yami and Vangeans as sacrifices.
Captain Yami.
When that's done, the advent of Klyphoth will begin, lasting for seven days.
Seven levels, with seven gates, will open one by one.
Scattered throughout these gates are ten devils, each compatible with the Klyphoth.
The deeper the level, the stronger the enemies will be.
The upper ones are about as powerful as the Dark Triad members.
But as you descend, they become much fiercer.
What's worse?
If the final devil, Lucifero, emerges, this world is done for.
Yami and Vangeans will be killed by this process.
But as the catalysts, they'll be kept alive until the last gate opens.
Impressive.
He managed to gain this much information on his own.
And from the very heart of the enemy's country, no less.
But why would the Dark Triad want to attempt something that's so dangerous?
It isn't the kind of thing we could ever understand.
As Magic Knights, I'm sure you've met more than your share of people like them.
Those who care only about themselves and hurt without hesitation to satisfy their own desire.
Who feel no guilt or shame no matter how low they sink.
Personally, I would never even want to understand what motivates them.
They are the worst sort of trash imaginable.
Irrational evil.
There's nothing I hate more.
Perhaps God and the devils will forgive them for what they've done.
But I never will.
That being said, I can't defeat the Dark Triad without help.
I'm aware of my own limitations.
I won't attempt something beyond my abilities.
Which is why...
I'll make him the warrior we need.
We'll harness the potential of his anti-magic.
In three days, the Gate to the Underworld will be opened.
Before that happens, we're going to take back Yami and Vangeance and destroy the Tree of Klyphov.
Using my magic, we'll be able to infiltrate their castle without being detected.
Once inside, we'll attack the Dark Triad and take each of them down.
Dante has gravity and body magic.
Vanica has curse warding and blood magic.
Xenon has spatial and bone magic.
Xenon.
I won't be able to take many people with me.
We need to select a group that has the best chance of success against the devils, with Asta at its center.
Yeah! No wonder you're here then!
Clearly squad captains are the ones you want for this kind of thing!
Let me go.
I know it's impudent to ask.
But please, let me join you.
Are you stupid?
Like hell we're gonna send anyone who's already lost to them!
Yuno.
I understand how you feel right now.
But staying behind to protect the Clover Kingdom is also a vital task.
Yuno.
Actually, I did want to ask you something.
There's a resistance movement in the Spade Kingdom that seeks to undermine the Dark Triad's rule.
Not long ago, a member of this movement snuck across the border and into Clover.
He's at your hideout now, isn't he?
What's this?
Tell me, who are you really?
Apparently, I'm the Prince of the Spade Kingdom.
Prince!
No freaking way!
Come on!
You're not serious about this, are you?
No freaking way!
Come on!
You're not serious about this, are you?
Yes.
I was a newborn when the royal family was overthrown.
Someone smuggled me out and brought me to Clover.
I see.
He's royalty.
That explains the tremendous amount of mana he has.
The man you mentioned before.
He was loyal to the previous rulers of Spade.
He should know a great deal about the enemy and the castle.
Yeah!
That's even more reason not to let you in on this!
For all we know, that guy's an enemy spy!
And not just him either!
Who says you're not a spy yourself?
If I don't save him, then there's no point.
You don't understand.
Since the elves attacked, you've been cautious.
You weren't sure you could still trust Captain Vongens.
And I can't blame you for that.
He couldn't choose between the humans and the elves.
And our kingdom suffered.
But that's exactly why, no matter how much he's hurting,
he continues to fight more earnestly than anyone else.
I was defeated by Xenon.
But I remember, as I was blacking out,
while he fought,
Captain Vongens did his best to keep the Golden Dawn safe.
If you rid yourself of some of that baggage,
you'd be able to focus more of your strength on our battle.
But you won't do that, will you?
And that's exactly why you're going to lose.
Of course I won't abandon them.
I made them walk a path of thorns, but they rose again.
They forged ahead without resentment or regret.
They are all I could ask them to be!
They are my dream!
He was only captured because he was protecting us.
He could have saved himself, but he didn't.
Maybe to you he's a traitor who once turned his back on this kingdom.
But to us he's not.
He's everything a squad captain should be.
You know.
That monster thinks he annihilated the Golden Dawn.
He's wrong.
Thanks to the captain's magic, we're alive and ready to fight back.
This war is far from over.
The Golden Dawn is still standing.
The greatest magic knight squad in the Clover Kingdom!
I'm going to prove that he did the right thing when he protected us.
They'll see just how powerful we are.
I will be the one who saves Captain Vongence.
The hell's up with this mana?
Enough!
Just sit down and shut up already, will ya?
Instead, how about you shut up?
I'm kind of busy storing up mana here.
We're going to take down that bony bastard!
Yuna won't lose to him again!
Very well, Yuren.
I don't actually hate people like you.
You may be the Prince of the Spade Kingdom and the Vice-Captain of the Golden Dawn,
but you'll always be Yuno to me.
In three days, we'll depart early in the morning for the Spade Kingdom.
I'll send you a more detailed plan later on.
This time, we're on the offensive.
Now that I see how Yuno's handling this, I understand there's no time to cry.
If I was too weak to win, that means I need to be stronger.
No.
I'll push past my limits and become the strongest.
Let's go defeat the Dark Triad and save both our captains.
Right.
In that case, we'd better reach out to Heart for assistance as well.
I've tried, but they haven't answered me all day.
What?
Do you think something happened to Charmy and everyone else?
Yesterday, each Dark Triad member left their castle.
Knowing that, I'd wager Vanica went off to attack the Heart Kingdom.
You think so?
I don't believe it.
胸にしまい込んだままの想いを解き放って その翼を広げて one more time
今飛び立て あの海原を見下ろして 誰よりも遠く 何度でも Will you fly?
Beautiful どんな景色も 君といれば輝くよ だからずっとそばに
Beautiful and never let go 僕のこの手を離さないで どこまでも ついてきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
No way! So the vice-captain of the black bulls can use devil power too? Okay! What kind of training are we gonna do to make me the best?
Black Clover page 169 The Devil Binding Ritual